What is this?
This is weird...
My body is...
Why, you!
Just so you know,
I only specialize in bomb making.
You'll have to take it up with
someone else to change him ba—
It's okay.
You have time.
I made it so that his composition
slowly but surely absorbs oxygen.
Enjoy the slow, steady approach of that moment when he explo—
He doesn't mean it, right?
My body isn't going to...
I can't... move... It's hard...
to talk...
Do not move.
Alphonse Elric,
I don't know what has
happened to your body.
If you carelessly stimulate it—
You'd best not touch him, scarred man.
Homunculus!
Homunculus?
The only thing your arm is capable of is destruction.
Edward would be able to transmute the boy into another material
and should be able to
prevent him from exploding.
Transmute him...
into another material?
Let's go.
I thought that your objective was to create a Philosopher's Stone.
You really aren't that woman.
There is no way that
she would say such a thing.
Shut up...
Stop...
Make that thing shut up.
Get up... and walk!
Move... forward!
Shut up!
Ed!
Rose! Get back!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Dammit!
I'm not going to allow you to use that arm for any more alchemy!
Shut up!
Stop that, Edward.
Come over here.
Ed!
Don't!
I've been wondering
about you for a while now.
You look too much like her.
But I've been trying to keep myself from thinking about it...
Trying not to think about it...
On that day, did we...
create you?
Ed!
If so, then you...
are our sin!
A homunculus...
So you've infiltrated
the military, have you?
For what purpose?
Don't you lay a hand on her!
Let's go, Rose.
You went too easy on them.
Homunculi have more than just one life.
It will take more than that to finish them off.
That was amazing, Rose!
Your voice is back.
You're right.
Thanks to both you and your
baby's voices, I was spared...
I can't reach Kimbly.
Nor your Chimeras.
They are on a special mission from the Führer.
Does it really take this long
just to find Fullmetal's corpse
and bring it back here?
Did he and Scar end up
killing each other?
Or is he just out having fun
destroying things?
I can't stand this waiting!
So this is your command center,
is it, Archer?
You're out of line, Mustang!
Don't move!
Hi.
What was that?
How mean!
Lieutenant!
Relax.
He's...
Yes, he is.
Shou Tucker,
the Sewing Life Alchemist.
You, huh?
I guess you couldn't go along with my methods, then?
I don't remember ever
supporting you to begin with.
I just had to dip myself in the sludge in order to get the corruption
that's rampant throughout the military
to rise to the surface.
There's no such thing as a military that
doesn't have any corruption or evil within it.
Tucker!
What good does it do you,
pulling a stupid stunt like this?!
As you were recognized
once upon a time in Ishbal,
today, I will be the hero.
Hey, hey!
They're gonna die. They're gonna die.
They're all gonna die, huh?
I guess the depth of
that person's thoughts
is lost on the likes of humans.
No matter.
As long as they get rid of Scar.
Then again, if they are to become ingredients for the Philosopher's Stone...
The Philosopher's Stone? They're gonna make it?
There's no way it will
fall into the hands of men.
In other words,
it won't even exist.
I'm sorry, but I can't
remember anything.
I wasn't expecting you to.
You are not the woman my brother was trying to bring back to life.
You just look like her, that's all.
Once I become human with the
Philosopher's Stone, it will be the same thing.
No, it won't.
What will be different about it?
That which is dead
does not come back to life.
What are you planning to do?
Just a minute!
Stay back!
Just be quiet and watch.
What have you done?
I inherited this arm
from my brother.
My brother turned himself into a transmutation circle
and sealed up the lives of the
Ishbalan people within himself.
In order to transmute the
Philosopher's Stone inside himself.
And then it was taken on by you.
Then...
Do not go near him.
There is nothing
you can do now but watch.
Are you out of your mind?
You intend to turn this boy
into the Philosopher's Stone?!
There isn't any time.
Unless I change his whole body into
some other material, he will explode.
So you're making him
the Philosopher's Stone?
Are you sure you want to hand
a Philosopher's Stone over to them?
I don't even know
if I will succeed.
If it is to be, then it will be theirs.
They may do as they wish with it.
I can't have that.
I need you to create a genuine Philosopher's Stone.
Don't do anything so absurd
as to transmute that boy's body.
If you kill me here and now, will your wish be fulfilled?
Fine, then.
If he does create the genuine article, I'll just use it right there and then.
It's no concern of mine what happens to the younger brother, after all.
Brother... stop... Scar-san...
At this rate, you'll be able to reach a town farther away.
You're going now?
You'll have to manage somehow.
I'm going to go catch Scar.
It's Scar that the military is after.
You're going to turn Scar over to the military?
That's probably the only way the military will let the people of Liore off the hook.
No, Ed, you can't...
You know why, don't you?
Equivalent... exchange.
Maybe there's something I can do.
I don't know.
Maybe if I tell the Colonel
about the Führer's secretary from earlier, and then...
whatever, make some
kind of deal with him.
Still, don't count on it, okay?
In any case, get out of here.
As far as you can get,
before the military realizes.
Right.
That was the plan
from the start.
We'll split up into small groups
and slip our way into
other cities someplace.
I'm counting on you, Lyra.
Rose.
See you later, Ed.
Yeah.
No,
this is good-bye, Rose.
There's no sign of anyone!
Could they be planning a sneak attack?
What's that?
There's someone there!
Colonel!
What's that?
Is that...
That's a State Alchemist!
It's Scar! Scar is there!
That bastard!
He murdered the
State Alchemist who went in to talk to him!
Have the tank division
surround the city!
Infantrymen, capture Scar!
Forward!
The military was not
supposed to move in.
In that case,
it must be the will of God.
There he is!
You fool.
I can't die that easily.
I knew that...
but my body moved on its own...
You were in love...
with me?
Not with you...
I hated my brother.
He turned his back on the teachings of Ishbala and studied alchemy.
Despite knowing that he gave me his arm so that I would survive,
I still couldn't help but hate him.
The Elric brothers...
each live for the other.
Yes.
The older loves the younger,
and the younger loves the older.
I also wanted to tell...
my older brother...
that I loved him.
Which is why you're doing for that younger brother
what your older brother
did for you, right?
Now, get going.
The despicable act
is about to begin.
I don't even know
your real name...
Our names are something
that are given to us by God.
However, as someone who
has turned his back on God,
I no longer have a name.
There he is! It's Scar!
After him!
Yes, sir!
Farewell, Scar.
Stop!
You're safe?
The citizens of Liore surrender!
Scar is the only one left!
Surrender? I don't believe it.
They killed the Crimson Alchemist.
Is that what your just cause is?!
The war has begun.
You can go ahead and die yourself if you want,
but don't send those clueless soldiers in there in the name of your worthless lust for glor—
We've spotted someone who appears to be Scar!
We are engaging him now!
All right!
Stop!
Hey, wait! Stop!
Brother...
"Those who give pain cannot sleep."
However, I need not worry about that any longer.
I shall never seek sleep again.
Brother...
Wh-What is that?
What is that?!
Colonel!
You stupid bastards!
Are you all right?
More or less.
Did Colonel Archer
take the division?
Y-Yes...
and there's something strange about that...
The town of Liore
lit up a deep red.
And we can't contact the division.
What was that?
What just happened here?
Hurry and carry away
those who are still alive.
Scar!
Al...
Brother?
Brother, no! Stay back! I'm going to explode!
Huh?
Al...
What are you doing here?
Huh?
I'm back to normal?
Brother, I'm back!
My body is back to normal!
Huh?
I don't know
what's going on here.
Oh, right.
I was turned into
a bomb by Kimbly.
But Scar-san said that if my armor
were transmuted into something else,
I would be spared, so he...
Al, open up your belly.
Just open it!
Brother, what is this?
Al...
Moments ago, a transmutation circle
was activated in the city.
Scar has transmuted
a Philosopher's Stone.
Not inside himself...
Yes, that's right, boy.
Little Brother,
you have been transmuted
into the Philosopher's Stone.
I'm... the Philosopher's Stone?
What's going on here?!
Why would he do such a thing?!
Go on.
Soon, they will be after you, and then everything will be set in motion.
Didn't you want the
Philosopher's Stone as well?
Brother...
I'm...
Al...
Fullmetal Alchemist...
Episode 43: "The Stray Dog"
I'm sorry, Colonel.
But we will come back.